[{
    "theme": "Colores ðŸŽ¨",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "What is the word for 'red' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["rojo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'yellow' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["amarillo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'orange' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["naranja"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'pink' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["rosa"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'fuchsia pink' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["rosa fucsia"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'purple' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["morado"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'violet' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["violeta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'green' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["verde"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'blue' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["azul"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'light blue' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["azul claro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'dark blue' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["azul oscuro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'black' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["negro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'white' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["blanco"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'gray' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["gris"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the word for 'brown' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["marrÃ³n"]
        }
    ]
}]
